National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; 1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; 1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Noguera, William Adolf (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Noland, John (NC), 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Norris, Larry (AR), 2005 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Nuncio, Paul (TX), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Oats Jr., Soonie (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Ockenhouse, John (PA), 2001 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - O'Dell, Joseph (VA), 1996; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Odle, James (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Oken, Steven H. (MD), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Oliver, Anthony (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - O'Malley, James Francis (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Orme, Roderick M. (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - O'Rourke, Michael (AR), 2000; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Ortiz, Ignacio (AZ), 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Owens, Gaille (TN), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Owsley, Michael (MO), 2002 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Oxford, Richard (MO), 1996; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Palma, Jimmy (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Palmer, Charles J. (NE), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Panah, Hooman Ashkan (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Pardo, Manuel (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Parker, Frank (AR), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Parker, J.B, (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Parsons, Joseph (UT), 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Paset, John (CT), 2005 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Patterson, Raymond (SC), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Payne, Eric (VA), 1998 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Payne, Pervis (TN), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Paz, Federico (ID), 2005 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Peede, Robert (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Pelzer, Kevin (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Pennington, Michael (OK), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Penry, John (TX), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Perry, Eugene (AR), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Perry, James Edward (MD), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Perry, Michael O. (LA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Petary, Donald (MO), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Peterica, Daniel (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Peterkin, Otis (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Pettit, Samuel (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Phillips, Allen Wayne (AL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Phillips, Richard "Speed" (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Pinholster, Scott (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Pittman, David (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Plantz, Marilyn (OK), 2001; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Plath, John (SC), 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Poland, Michael (AZ), 1998; 2005; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Poland, Patrick Gene (AZ), 2000 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Pollard, Roosevelt (MO), 1997; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Pollock, Milton (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Pope, Carlton Jerome (VA) Executed August 19, 1997, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Porter, Raleigh (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Powell, Carl Devon (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Powell, Ozie (AL), 1996 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Powell, Reginald (MO), 1998 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Power, Robert (FL), 1990 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Preston, Elroy (MO), 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Preston, Robert (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Price, Christopher (AL), 1993 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Prince, Cleophus Jr. (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Prince, Curtis (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Provenzano, Thomas H. (FL), 2005; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Pruet, Marion (AR), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Puiatti, Carl (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Pyles, Johnny (TX) Executed June 15, 1998 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Quesinberry, George (VA), 1999; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Quintanilla, Jessie (Military), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Quintero, Derrick (TN), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Ragon, Derrick (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Rainey, Michael (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Raley, David Allen (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Ramdass, Bobby Lee (VA), 2000 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Ramirez, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Ramsey, Roy (MO), 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Ransom, Kenneth (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Ray, Johnny Babe Jr. (SC), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Reams, Kenneth (AR), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Rector, Charles (TX), 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Rector, Ricky (AR), 2005 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Red Dog, James A. (DE), 2005 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Reese, John (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Reeves, Randolph (NE), 1996; 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Reid, Anthony (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Reid, Lloyd (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Remata, Daniel (FL), 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Renfro, Steven C. (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Reyes, Angel (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Rice, David L. (WA), 2005 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Rich, Darrell (CA), 2000 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Richardson, Antonio (MO), 2001; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Richardson, Miguel (TX), 2000 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Richey, Kenneth T. (OH), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Richley, Darryl V. (AR) Executed August 3, 1994, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Riddle, Ernest M. (SC), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Riechmann, Dieter (FL), 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Riggs, Christina (AR), 2000 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Riley, James (DE), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Riley, Leandress (CA), 1998 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Riley, Michael (TX), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Ring, Timothy (AZ), 2002 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Rios, Miguel (PA), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Rivera, Michael (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Rivers, Delores (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Roach, Steven (VA), 1999 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Robb, Jason (OH), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Robbins, Malcolm (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Robedeaux, James (OK), 2000; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Roberts, Michael Donald (OK), 2000; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Roberts, Rickey (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Roy (MO), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Sammy D. (SC) September 25, 1998, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Robertson, Andrew E. (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Robinson, Antyane (PA), 1999 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Robinson, James, Jr. (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Robison, Larry (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Roche, Charles E. Jr (IN), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Rocheville, David (SC), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Rodrigues, Jose A. (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Rodrigues, Luis (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Rodriguez, Frank (CO), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Rodriguez, Toribio R. (AZ), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Rogers, Dayton Leroy (OR), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Rogers, Glen (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Rogers, Kelly (OK), 2000 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Rogers, Patrick (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Rogovich, Pete Carl (AZ), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Rojem, Richard Norman (OK), 1993 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Rolan, Florencio (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Roldan, Ricardo (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Rolling, Danny (FL), 1993; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Romano, John (OK), 2001; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Rompilla, Ronald (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Rose, James (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Rose, Milo (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Ross, Arthur M. (AZ), 1998 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Ross, Bobby (OK), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Ross, Michael Bruce (CT), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Routier, Darlie (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Rowland, Guy Kevin (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Royal, Thomas (VA), 1999 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Roybal, Rudolph (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Ruescher, ED (MO), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Ruiz, Alejandro Gilbert (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Running, Eagle, Sean Bernard (AZ), 1993 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Russell, Willie C. (MS), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Ryan, Michael (NE), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Sagastegui, Jeremy V. (WA), 1998; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Salazar, Maximo (OK), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Salcido, Ramon (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Samuels, Mary (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Sanborn, Paramore (KY), 1991; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Sanchez-Velasco, Rigoberto (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Sanders, Raymond (AR), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Sanders, Reginald N. (DE), 2005 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Sanders, Ronald (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Sanderson, Ricky L. (NC), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Sandoval, Alfred (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Santellan, Jose (TX), 2002 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Santiago, Salvador Carlos (PA), 1992 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Saranchek, Daniel (PA), 2000; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Sasser, Andrew (AR), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Satcher, Michael C. (VA) Executed December 9, 1997, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Saunders, William (VA), 1999 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Savino, Joseph (VA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Saylor, Benny (IN), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Scanlon, Donald (NC), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Schurz, Eldon M. (AZ), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Schwab, Mark (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Scott, Jay D. (OH), 2001; 2005 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Scott, Paul (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Sexton, Michael Earl (NC), 2000; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Sharp, Michael (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Shaw, Bobby L. (MO), 2005; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Sheldon, Jeffrey (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Shelton, Steven (DE), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Shepard, Mark (VA), 1999 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Shepphard, Bobby Terrell (OH), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Sheridan, Darrell (AR), 1993; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Shields, Robert (TX), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Sibley, George (AL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Silva, Benjamin Wai (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Simon, Robert Jr. (MS), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Sims, Mitchell (SC), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Sims, Terry Melvin (SC), 2000; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Singleton, Charles (AR), 1998; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Singleton, Fred (SC), 2005; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Sireci, Henry (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Siripongs, Jaturun (CA), 1998; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Six, Andrew (MO), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Skaggs, David (KY), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Slaughter, James Earl (KY), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Slaughter, Michael Corey (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Slawson, Newton Carlton (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Smallwood, Dion (OK), 2000 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Smith, Andrew (SC), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Smith, Brian (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Smith, Bruce (VA), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Smith, Clay (AR), 2001 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Smith, Clifford (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Smith, Frank E. (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Smith, Frank Lee (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Smith, Gregory Scott (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Smith, James Edward (TX), 2005 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Smith, James W. (AL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Smith, Joe (AZ), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Smith, John Eldon (GA) Executed December 15, 1983, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Smith, Oscar (TN), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Smith, Phillip D. (OK), 2001; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Smith, Rickie (TX), 1999 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Smith, Robert Douglas (AZ), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Smith, Robert (IN), 1998; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Smith, Roderick Lynn (OK), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Smith, Samuel (MO), 2001; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Smith, Tommie (IN), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Smith, William H. (OH), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Smith, Willie Albert (MS), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Snell, Richard W. (AR) Executed April 19, 1995, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Socher, Dennis (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Sockwell, Michael (AL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Soloman, Morris (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - South, Robert W. (SC) Executed May 31, 1996, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Sowell, Billie J. (OH), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Spann, Sterling (SC), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Spence, David (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Spencer, Clinton L. (AZ), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Spinelli, Juanita (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Spirko, John (OH), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Spivey, Ronald (GA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Spotz, Mark (PA), 1999; 2001 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Stager, Barbara (NC), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Stanely, Gerald Frank (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Stankewitz, Douglas (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Stano, Gerald (FL), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Stansbury, Robert E. (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Staten, De, Ondre (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Sterling, Gary (TX), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Stevens, Charles Arnett (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Steward, Raymond (IL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Stewart, Kenneth (VA) September 23, 1998, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Stewart, Walter (IL), 1997; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Stoker, David (TX), 1997 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Stokes, Ralph (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Stone, Benjamin (TX) Executed September 25, 1997, Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Stout, Larry (VA), 1996 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Strouth, Donald (TN), 2002; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Styron, Ronford (TX), 2002; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Sullivan, Willie (DE), 1999; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Sully, Anthony (CA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Sutton, Nicholas (TN), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Swafford, Roy (FL), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 152)
    - Swann, Calvin E. (VA), 1999; 2005 (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 153)
    - Sweet, Glennon P. (MO), 1998; Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 154)
    - Szuchon, Joseph (PA), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 155)
    - Tamme, Frank (KY), Undated (Box 8 (1-Case Files), Folder 156)
    - Tankersley, Bobby (AZ), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Tarver, Robert (AL), 2000; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Tassin, Robert (LA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Tate, Gregory (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Feltus (LA), 1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Freddie (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Michael A. (MO), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Richard (TN), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Taylor, Robert (T-Bone) (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Taylor, Victor (KY), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Teffeteller, Robert (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Thanos, John (MO), 2005 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Thomas, Andrew (TN), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Thomas, Patrcia (AL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Thompson, Catherine (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Thompson, Gregory (TN), 2005 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Louis (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Thompson, Robert Jackson (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Thompson, Steven A. (AL), 1998 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Thompson, Thomas M. (CA), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Thompson, William Wayne (OK), 1996 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Thornton, Mark Scott (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Tigner, Gerald (TX), 2002; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Timberlake, Norman H. (IN), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Tokar, Jeffrey (MO), 2002 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Toles, Bryan A. (OK), 1993 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Tompkins, Wayne (FL), 2001; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Torrence, Michael (SC), 1996; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Travaglia, Michael (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Trawuck, Jack Harrison (AL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Trease, Robert (FL), 2002 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Trepal, George (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Trevino, Joe (TX), 1999 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Trice, Eddoe Leroy (OK), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Trop, Albert (NY), 2002 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Truesdale, Louis (SC) December 11, 1998, Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Tucker, Karla Faye (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Tucker, Karla Faye (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Tuggle Jr., Cem (VA), 1996; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Tuilaepa, Paul P. (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Turner, Jessel (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Turner, Melvin (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Turner, William (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Turrentine, Kenneth (OK), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Tuttle, Charles (TX), 1999 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Twenzer, Virginia Ann (MO), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Valdes, Frank (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Valdez, Gerardo (OK), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Vann, Gissie Willis (TN), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Van Poyck, William (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Van Woundenberg, Sammy (OK), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Vickers, Robert (AZ), 1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Victor, Clarence (NE), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Villafuerte, Jose R. (AZ), 1998; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Vondohlen, Herman H. (SC), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Wade, Melvin (CA), 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Waldon, Billy Ray (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Walker, Charles (IL), 2005 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Walker, Dale Alan (MS), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Walker, Gary A. (OK), 1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Walker, Marvin (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Walker, Maxine (AL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Wallace, George K. (OK), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Wallace, Jim (AZ), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Wallace, Valorie (KY), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Wallace, William (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Walker, Shawn (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Walters, Christina (NC), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Walton, Jason (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Walton, Jeffrey Alan (AZ), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Walton, Percy L. (VA), 2005 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Ward, Thomas Lee (LA) Executed May 16, 1995, Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Ware, Darris (MD), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)